<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>BLOG_NAME</title>
 <link href="YOUR_URL/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="YOUR_URL"/>
 <updated>2014-11-23T17:45:57-06:00</updated>
 <id>BLOG_URL</id>
 <author>
   <name>BLOG_NAME</name>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>A much needed Respite in Minneapolis</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/2014/11/23/a-much-needed-respite/"/>
   <updated>2014-11-23T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/2014/11/23/a-much-needed-respite</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We just came off a wonderful two-day stint in Minneapolis, MN. We were pretty exhausted heading into Minnesota, and the weather had
taken a turn for the worst. Thankfully, we were able to rest up at the beautiful house of Anne and David F., right on Lake Riley.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/anne_and_david.jpg&quot; title=&quot;With our lovely hosts&quot; alt=&quot;With our lovely hosts&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One morning we woke up to a pileated woodpecker in the backyard and a bald eagle fishing on the lake. We learned about ice
boating, maple syrup, and Swarm. We&#39;re incredibly thankful to Anne and David for their generosity and hospitality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who knew Minnesota had a coffee scene? We weren&#39;t able to try all of the coffee roasters in town, but we checked out Dogwood,
Bull Run, and Five Watt. We were most impressed with Five Watt, followed by Dogwood. Bull Run has a nice vibe - it seems
like a place to study while sipping a sweetened latte - but the coffee didn&#39;t live up to the others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minneapolis had some good Chinese and Vietnamese food too! We really enjoyed the city, and if their tech scene is as good as
their food scene, we might have to check out their job listings...&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Our Hike Through the White Mountains</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/2014/11/12/indian-head/"/>
   <updated>2014-11-12T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/2014/11/12/indian-head</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This was a couple weeks back, but I finally found time to blog about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; We did it! &lt;/strong&gt; We hiked the Mount Pemigewasset via Indian Head Trail with an 1557 feet elevation gain. This is a panorama of the view from the top with my crappy camera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/indian_head.jpg&quot; title=&quot;View from the top of Mt. Pemigewasset&quot; alt=&quot;View from the top of Mt. Pemigewasset&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>An Answer to a Common Question</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/2014/11/05/reasons/"/>
   <updated>2014-11-05T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/2014/11/05/reasons</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;When we tell people that we quit our jobs to go on a road trip for 6 months, the most common question is: “So...was there something that sparked this trip?” I think it&#39;s really interesting so many people have asked us this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I&#39;m going to try to answer this. I wouldn&#39;t say there was a specific moment that sparked this. Rather, Gabe and I have just been talking about this for a long time, and there really isn&#39;t ever a perfect time for something like this. We didn&#39;t have a family nor were we tied town to anything permanent. I knew if we didn&#39;t do it, it would always be a lingering “what if?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find that my life perspective changes every time I travel. Suddenly, the little things don&#39;t matter as much. You reconnect with hobbies you used to love and find out new things about yourself you didn&#39;t know before. I could spend X years at a company, hoping those 2 weeks of vacation come faster. ...Or I could go on a road trip. I&#39;m not saying everyone should quit their jobs, but I do think that there is something to be said about the occasional trip. It&#39;s almost like a proverbial reset button. With that being said, it&#39;s been really nice thinking about what makes me happy and what I want to do going forward.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>YC Application Submitted!</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/2014/10/15/yc-application/"/>
   <updated>2014-10-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/2014/10/15/yc-application</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday night we submitted our application for YC!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you that don&#39;t know, YCombinator is one of the most prestigious startup accelerators in the US. It&#39;s a
venture capital firm that provides support and community to its founders. We&#39;re applying with an idea for a language
learning product that we&#39;re calling Linguistik.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most important piece of language learning is finding an opportunity to converse with native speakers. We think
there&#39;s a lot of room for improvement in the current tools to find a language partner. There&#39;s not a great way to find
a partner with similar interests, values, and skills. This is particularly frustrating because great matchmaking tools
 exist already - they&#39;re just applied to dating or social networking products. Linguistik is a social matchmaking product
 to automatically match its users with compatible partners who can provide productive and engaging language practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now the team is just Jenn and I. She&#39;ll lead design and product, and I&#39;ll lead development. Version 1 will be a
webapp written with Rails. I&#39;ll have a launch page and eventually a prototype up online at getlinguistik.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would be wonderful to get into YC, but we know it&#39;s impossible to count on that. Either way, it was great to
experience the application process, and we&#39;re excited to build out the product. We&#39;ll give more updates as progress
continues!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>We're going on a road trip!</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/2014/10/11/were-going-on-a-road-trip/"/>
   <updated>2014-10-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/2014/10/11/were-going-on-a-road-trip</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The road trip begins!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Gabe and I quit our jobs. We terminated our lease and I sold my car. Essentially, we were homeless, and I&#39;ve never been so excited! We&#39;re going on a road trip across the United States and part of Canada! Before this road trip, my idea of “roughing it” was sleeping on the floor at a friends place. But since we no longer have jobs, we decided to camp at different state parks, stay at friend&#39;s places, and couchsurf to save money. Gabe had never camped before, and I had only done festival camping for 2 nights in which other people set up the tent for me. So, it&#39;ll be quite the experience sleeping outside in the cold!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our first night of camping was at Pine Grove Furnace State Park. The mid-point of the Appalachian Trail actually runs through the park! We got there at around 9pm, so it was really dark setting up the tent. There were a few mistakes, but we&#39;ll do better next time =P. We ended up setting up the tent on a slight slope and we forgot to clear the small rocks and nuts from the ground before we set up the tent. I sleep on my side, so I kept rolling into Gabe in the middle of the night. It ended up being fine, but a bit of a rough night&#39;s sleep. Pretty good for the first night of camping in my opinion!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://farm3.staticflickr.com/2948/15315030287_fa952ba56a_h.jpg&quot; title=&quot;First Night Camping&quot; alt=&quot;First Night Camping&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our journey so far:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saline, Michigan &gt; Pittsburgh, PA &gt; Pine Grove Furnace State Park &gt; Hershey, PA &gt; Philadelphia, PA &gt; New York City&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Quitting and Blogging</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/2014/10/07/quitting-and-blogging/"/>
   <updated>2014-10-07T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/2014/10/07/quitting-and-blogging</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Writing is tough. As time goes on, it seems like eloquence is harder and harder to come by.
I&#39;m hoping that a public-facing blog will motivate me not only to write regularly, but also to consciously improve my writing.
For now, the only goal I&#39;m setting for myself is to contribute to this blog at least once a week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plan to write about software, traveling, food, and whatever else comes to mind.
It&#39;s worth noting that Jenn will be writing as well, and there&#39;s no guarantee of coordination between our posts and/or topics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here goes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s hard to know at this point whether I made the right decision in leaving Yahoo. I can&#39;t imagine a better place
to start my career as a software developer, and I&#39;m so grateful for all that I learned in my 14 months in Sunnyvale.
I worked with some of the smartest people I&#39;ve ever met, and I learned more about software and computer science than
I had through 4 years of coursework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working on Yahoo Mail meant that my focus at work was entirely on the back-end of one product. This meant that the
primary focus of my life was the back-end of Yahoo Mail. Those 14 months were likely the most productive months of
my life. However, I also put my personal projects and passions on the back burner. I left Yahoo to travel and work
full-speed on a project relating to my love of language. I hope to gain experience that is harder to gain at a large
tech company:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing a product driven by passion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Taking a product from 0 to 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning non-software aspects of a product, e.g. design and finance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Jenn and I will be applying to Y Combinator next week. We know how competitive YC is. The experience of applying will
be valuable in itself and will act to motivate us in the development of a prototype. I look forward to building a
product from scratch with a partner as wonderful and capable as Jenn.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>