<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>BLOG_NAME</title>
 <link href="YOUR_URL/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="YOUR_URL"/>
 <updated>2014-10-13T02:36:38-04:00</updated>
 <id>BLOG_URL</id>
 <author>
   <name>BLOG_NAME</name>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>We're going on a road trip!</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/2014/10/11/were-going-on-a-road-trip/"/>
   <updated>2014-10-11T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/2014/10/11/were-going-on-a-road-trip</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The road trip begins!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Gabe and I quit our jobs. We terminated our lease and I sold my car. Essentially, we were homeless, and I&#39;ve never been so excited! We&#39;re going on a road trip across the United States and part of Canada! Before this road trip, my idea of “roughing it” was sleeping on the floor at a friends place. But since we no longer have jobs, we decided to camp at different state parks, stay at friend&#39;s places, and couchsurf to save money. Gabe had never camped before, and I had only done festival camping for 2 nights in which other people set up the tent for me. So, it&#39;ll be quite the experience sleeping outside in the cold!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our first night of camping was at Pine Grove Furnace State Park. The mid-point of the Appalachian Trail actually runs through the park! We got there at around 9pm, so it was really dark setting up the tent. There were a few mistakes, but we&#39;ll do better next time =P. We ended up setting up the tent on a slight slope and we forgot to clear the small rocks and nuts from the ground before we set up the tent. I sleep on my side, so I kept rolling into Gabe in the middle of the night. It ended up being fine, but a bit of a rough night&#39;s sleep. Pretty good for the first night of camping in my opinion!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://farm3.staticflickr.com/2948/15315030287_fa952ba56a_h.jpg&quot; title=&quot;First Night Camping&quot; alt=&quot;First Night Camping&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our journey so far:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saline, Michigan &gt; Pittsburgh, PA &gt; Pine Grove Furnace State Park &gt; Hershey, PA &gt; Philadelphia, PA &gt; New York City&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Quitting and Blogging</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/2014/10/07/quitting-and-blogging/"/>
   <updated>2014-10-07T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/2014/10/07/quitting-and-blogging</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Writing is tough. As time goes on, it seems like eloquence is harder and harder to come by.
I&#39;m hoping that a public-facing blog will motivate me not only to write regularly, but also to consciously improve my writing.
For now, the only goal I&#39;m setting for myself is to contribute to this blog at least once a week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plan to write about software, traveling, food, and whatever else comes to mind.
It&#39;s worth noting that Jenn will be writing as well, and there&#39;s no guarantee of coordination between our posts and/or topics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here goes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s hard to know at this point whether I made the right decision in leaving Yahoo. I can&#39;t imagine a better place
to start my career as a software developer, and I&#39;m so grateful for all that I learned in my 14 months in Sunnyvale.
I worked with some of the smartest people I&#39;ve ever met, and I learned more about software and computer science than
I had through 4 years of coursework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working on Yahoo Mail meant that my focus at work was entirely on the back-end of one product. This meant that the
primary focus of my life was the back-end of Yahoo Mail. Those 14 months were likely the most productive months of
my life. However, I also put my personal projects and passions on the back burner. I left Yahoo to travel and work
full-speed on a project relating to my love of language. I hope to gain experience that is harder to gain at a large
tech company:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing a product driven by passion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Taking a product from 0 to 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning non-software aspects of a product, e.g. design and finance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Jenn and I will be applying to Y Combinator next week. We know how competitive YC is. The experience of applying will
be valuable in itself and will act to motivate us in the development of a prototype. I look forward to building a
product from scratch with a partner as wonderful and capable as Jenn.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>